{"id":"2018_17","name":"","memoryVerse":"\"The precepts of the Lord are right, giving joy to the heart. The commands of the Lord are radiant, giving light to the eyes.\" â€“ Psalm 19:8","dayQuestions":{"one":{"title":"FIRST DAY: Read the notes and the references.","questions":[{"id":"2018_17_1","questionText":"1. Use this space to record how you have seen God's activity during the week. (How has He provided, answered, comforted, reconciled, guided, etc.?)","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_17_2","questionText":"2. From the past week's study, what made the most significant impact to you in the notes, lecture, group sharing or personal study?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"two":{"title":"SECOND DAY: Read 2 Samuel 5:1-16.\nThe Lord established David as Israel's king.","readVerse":[{"book":"2 Samuel","verse":"5:1-16"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_17_3","questionText":"3. What reasons did Israel's tribes give for making David king? How did David's rise to power validate God's call and years of waiting? (1 Samuel 16:11-13)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"1 Samuel","verse":"16:11-13"}]},{"id":"2018_17_4","questionText":"4. What characteristics does David exhibit in these verses? What opportunities is God giving you to develop these characteristics?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_17_5","questionText":"5. How did David understand the reason and purpose for his success? Where has God placed you so you will bless those around you?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"three":{"title":"THIRD DAY: Read 2 Samuel 5:17-25 and Psalm 68.\nGod delivered David from the Philistines twice.","readVerse":[{"book":"2 Samuel","verse":"5:17-25"},{"book":"Psalm","verse":"68:1-999"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_17_6","questionText":"6. How did David respond to the Philistine threat? When have you recently prayed for wisdom and direction? What were the results?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_17_7","questionText":"7. From Psalm 68, for what attributes of God does David praise God?","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Psalm","verse":"68:1-999"}]},{"id":"2018_17_8","questionText":"8. What encourages or challenges you most about David's worship and understanding of God?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"four":{"title":"FOURTH DAY: Read 2 Samuel 6:1-11; 1 Chronicles 13:1-14.\nDavid disobeyed God's instructions for moving the ark.","readVerse":[{"book":"2 Samuel","verse":"6:1-11"},{"book":"1 Chronicles","verse":"13:1-14"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_17_9","questionText":"9. Why might David want the ark of the covenant in Jerusalem? Who confirmed his plans?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_17_10","questionText":"10. Why did God respond the way He did? What lessons do you learn? (Exodus 25:10-22; Numbers 4:5-6, 15)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Exodus","verse":"25:10-22"},{"book":"Numbers","verse":"4:5-6"},{"book":"Numbers","verse":"15:1-999"}]},{"id":"2018_17_11","questionText":"11. How has this study challenged or enlarged your view of God? How will this impact the way you live?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"five":{"title":"FIFTH DAY: Read 2 Samuel 6:12-23; 1 Chronicles 15:1-16:43.\nDavid brought the ark to Jerusalem with great celebration.","readVerse":[{"book":"2 Samuel","verse":"6:12-23"},{"book":"1 Chronicles","verse":"15:1-16:43"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_17_12","questionText":"12. What differences did you notice when the ark was moved the second time? What do you learn from that?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_17_13","questionText":"13. How did David celebrate his love and thankfulness to God? For what will you celebrate and thank God?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_17_14","questionText":"14. How did Michal respond to David's expressive worship? What can you learn from David's response when others ridicule you?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"six":{"title":"SIXTH DAY: Review 2 Samuel 5-6; 1 Chronicles 11:1-9; 12:1-16:43; Psalm 68.","readVerse":[{"book":"2 Samuel","verse":"5:1-6:999"},{"book":"1 Chronicles","verse":"11:1-9"},{"book":"1 Chronicles","verse":"12:1-16:43"},{"book":"Psalm","verse":"68:1-999"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_17_15","questionText":"15. What was your biggest takeaway from your personal study of this week's lesson?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]}}}